There's a question that I've asked myself over and over.
While I may proclaim to know who she is,
I may be missing something about Nagase Iori's true self on a fundamental level.
That question is "Who is Nagase Iori?"
This might be the worst time to do this,
but I have to tell you.
No.
I want to tell you.
I really do love you.
So please, will you go out with me?
I'm sorry.
I really am.
But I think something just isn't right.
So could you forget that I said I loved you?
Bye.
Wh-Why, Nagase?
I'm...
No.
I'm not the person Taichi thinks I am.
...gonna go.
February 14th.
Valentine's Day.
An air of sweet excitement has permeated Yamaboshi High School.
But after being turned down by Nagase yesterday, the air in my mind is bitter.
Hey, Yaegashi.
Why the long face?
You catch a cold or something?
You won't get any chocolate looking like that.
Frankly, this is a horrible time for me to be feeling depressed.
We're in the middle of our fourth supernatural phenomenon, courtesy of Balloon Vine.
Three days ago, Balloon Vine
appeared before us again.
Emotion transmission.
Simply put, no matter where you are, whether you want them to know or not,
your emotions will be transmitted to others.
So it's like a form of telepathy?
You could say that, but not really.
The phenomenon's timing will be completely random.
That includes whose emotions are transmitted, and to whom.
Those will change each time.
What does that mean?
What was that?
It was like Taichi's thoughts
suddenly echoed in my head.
Is that how this works?
Yes.
The person whose heart was
probed will know who received them.
But those on the receiving side will not know who else received them.
He's right.
I knew that my thoughts were transmitted to everyone.
Ah.
Well, that's all for me.
Oh.
If you have any questions, I can answer them now.
That thing from last time, The Second—what the hell was that?
Oh, that.
They've taken an interest in me.
In other words, I'm becoming more interesting.
But I don't really need to tell you about that, do I?
Anyway, I've explained the situation to you.
Until next time.
This isn't our first time dealing with him!
If we live our lives as we normally do, they'll leave us alone soon enough.
That's right.
They just want to watch us because they think we're interesting.
They'll stop all of this once they lose interest in us, right?
Yeah.
We'll be able to get through this one, too.
Don't you think so, too, Nagase?
Oh, uh... Yeah.
We can do it!
We'll pulverize Balloon Vine's plans and make it so they'll never screw with us again!
I'm getting fired up!
We've made it this far!
We'll be fine this time, too!
Yeah!
You do know you're the weakest link, right?
Huh?
Come on, Inaba-chan!
It's been three days since then.
We may be in the middle of this emotion transmission phenomenon,
but I don't want that to influence the decisions I make,
which is precisely why I asked Nagase to go out with me.
So could you forget that I said I loved you?
Could I have a word with you?
Yaegashi-kun, you're having love troubles, aren't you?
Today is Valentine's Day.
The biggest day for love in the year.
I can't have you bringing everyone down when they're practically walking on air.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Did Nagase-san reject you or something?
Wait, she did?
You looked like you were getting along just fine.
So she did...
I appreciate the sympathy, but you don't need to get depressed, too.
What a twist!
This is my chance!
Huh?!
Oh, I'm sorry.
I was so happy that I couldn't control myself.
You still haven't given up on Nagase?!
Just to set it straight,
I was only turned down!
You haven't won yet!
Yeah, yeah.
Keep crying, loser!
You bitch...
I mean, really?
You two were so lovey-dovey, and she rejected you?
That's hilarious!
Were you always like this?
You're looking better already.
Using face muscles you don't normally use is exhausting.
Did you do that...
to cheer me up?
So this is what they call a lucky break.
I'm still laughing inside.
So you really were just laughing at me.
Try to cheer up, Yaegashi-kun.
There's no point in moping around.
It's a good opportunity for you.
Why not try asking Inaba-san out?
Wait!
How do you know about me and Inaba?!
It couldn't be more obvious that she's in love.
It may have gone unnoticed to most, but not me.
For I am...
Class 1-3's Love God!
I hope you know that I fear you, Love God.
Now when should I give him my chocolate?
Inaba...
What's wrong?
Oh, nothing.
So, like I was saying, why not ask
Inaba-san out once you cheer up?
And while you're off working your magic on her, I'll take Nagase-san for myself!
I figured that was what you were after.
Taichi!
You're finally here!
We've got a problem on our hands.
What's wrong?
Did Balloon Vine do something?
No!
It's Gossan!
He might have to quit being our moderator!
O-Oh...
Wait, why?
Gossan's the moderator for both our club and the jazz band right now.
But next year, it's his turn to do something administrative.
He'll be busy, so he'll only be
able to moderate one club.
"Yeah, sure, change our moderator.
Fine by me," is what I'd like to say,
but there's Balloon Vine to consider.
Honestly, we couldn't ask for anyone better than Gotou since he doesn't come around here at all.
It'll be a problem if we get a serious teacher who actually checks on us every day.
Anyway, to get to the point,
whichever club earns more points at the end-of-year club presentations gets to keep Gotou.
The club presentations?
Oh, right. We have to do those, don't we?
Hey, how about we raid the jazz band's practice right now?
Iori-chan, you're a genius!
I definitely want to know what Gossan does over there!
Yeah.
Reconnaissance is a basic part of war!
See?
The jazz band has a good reason for wanting to keep Gotou-sensei.
Just wow, Gossan.
This is unreal.
So you were in the jazz band, Shiroyama-kun?
Yeah. I'm nowhere near the level of the other members, though.
Shiroyama-kun, don't be so modest!
You're the best player out of all the first-year members!
That's not true.
Shiroyama-kun's pretty popular.
I see why they call him "The Prince."
They said some pro bands want him, too.
You really can't judge a book by its cover.
Taking down that jazz band's going to be tough.
Hold up!
Okay, so we've been tossed into a
battle which we simply mustn't lose!
However, today is February 14th!
Don't you think there's something even more important that we should be thinking about, gentlemen?!
What?
Isn't anyone with me?
We're in the middle of this emotion transmission thing.
You don't need to bring up a topic like that.
Exactly my point!
We should tell each other now, before
everyone finds out at the most awkward time!
Well, I guess...
I just have to know who you're giving yours to, Inaba.
I've been dying to know ever since you asked me how to make chocolate a few days ago.
Seriously?!
Inaba-chan, there's a guy you're into?!
Well, um...
You expect me to tell everyone that I love Taichi at a time like this?!
Huh? What's wrong?
Did a transmission happen just now?
Oh, uh...
I thought there might be something
between you two, but...
D-Don't worry about it!
I knew I needed to tell you guys eventually, but I couldn't decide on a time.
So, yeah.
Iori and I are going head-to-head in seducing Taichi.
Funny, right? You could bust your gut!
Inaba-chan and Iori-chan...
over Taichi?
But don't worry!
It's not going to turn into anything messy!
Right, Iori? Taichi?
Y-Yeah, it'll be fine.
Though, I probably shouldn't say that...
...since I confessed to and got turned down by Nagase yesterday.
Flat out rejected.
Huh?
Huh?!
You all got that one, right?
Iori, he asked you out and you...
...turned him down?
What the hell?
Then what about my feelings?
No, I...
Sorry.
"Sorry"?!
Explain yourself, Iori!
Why the hell did you turn him down?!
Wait, Inaban, calm down.
Yeah, I turned him down, but I have my reasons.
I was going to tell you later, so...
It's none of her business.
Why's she snapping at me?
Huh?
Was that Iori?
I-I didn't mean that, Inaban!
I didn't mean to make it
sound like it's your problem!
What I meant was—
You're getting depressed when you're the one who snapped at me? Selfish much?
That's not what I meant either. It was a joke.
I guess I can't just brush it off like that, can I?
Completely different from what I thought.
Wait, I didn't—
Iori's scary!
Was Iori-chan always this kind of person?
No, I...
No, I didn't mean that, Iori!
Wh-What?
Did Iori-chan get something from you, Inaba-chan?
And so, Nagase Iori broke.
I'm home.
Welcome back, Onii-chan!
How was your day?
Get any chocolate?
What's wrong, Onii-chan?
Don't tell me you didn't even get a single piece!
Some people gave me a few out of obligation.
Oh, you'll be fine then.
Wait, I know what's wrong!
You didn't get any chocolate from the girl you like!
You probably saw her giving
some to some other guy, too!
Sorry. I'll talk to you later.
Wait! Seriously, tell me what's wrong!
Look, I have some chocolate for you, so cheer up!
This is my true love chocolate!
Thanks.
Huh? Aren't you gonna tell me what's wrong? Onii-chan?
Morning, Iori!
Oh, Nakayama-chan, morning!
So, did you give anyone chocolate yesterday?
Well, I did give some to a few people who I'm always causing trouble for, yeah.
No, I mean chocolate for someone you like!
You're really popular, you know?
Isn't there someone you have your eye on?
The only one I have eyes for, Mariko...
is you!
Oh my, Iori! I'm flattered!
What were you trying to say?
There's no deeper meaning to it.
He asked me out, and I rejected him. It's as simple as that.
Did something happen to make you fall out of love with him?
Why are you even bugging me about this?
Because I'm not convinced.
Not convinced about what?
Sorry, Inaban.
You might not understand, but I really don't want to go out with Taichi anymore.
So...
you really don't have to mind me.
Does it have anything to do with this emotion transmission thing?
Well, I can't say it has nothing to do with it...
Then rethink your decision!
We're in a weird situation right now.
Our decision-making is impaired.
Wait until we're back to normal, then—
When will that be?
Sure, this phenomenon will end eventually,
but what if another one occurs?
Then...
People are influenced by their experiences.
What's so different about Balloon Vine's
phenomena and other external influences?
This whole thing with Taichi and me wouldn't have started if we never experienced personality switching.
Was our decision-making impaired then, too?
Do you really want Taichi and me to start dating, anyway?
What do you want?
What should I do?
Nagase said that...
And then there's Inaba...
Did you get those too, Inaban?
Yeah.
We'll be late for school.
Let's go.
What was wrong with me just now?
Sorry I'm a day late.
Holy crap, I'm so happy that I could die!
Inaba.
Sorry to call you out like this.
I wanted to apologize for what happened yesterday.
You don't need to apologize.
All of that was my fault.
No, I was just kind of surprised.
I thought you would've said something to me before asking Iori out.
Well...
I was scared.
If I talked to Inaba, and she stopped me,
I wouldn't have been able to go through with it.
You...
You had trouble deciding between Iori and me?
N-No, you're wrong!
I am?
W-Well, you're not wrong, but...
I love Nagase.
But that doesn't mean I don't like you too.
I've never met someone as amazing as you.
R-Really? You said that pretty confidently.
I mean, you're really smart,
and you're always thinking about us.
And you're actually really nice.
You're mature, beautiful,
and kind of cute on top of that.
You might not be very athletic or good at cooking,
but the rest of you more than makes up for that.
W-Wait! Give me a second!
Okay. Keep going.
Huh? I don't really need to, do I?
Come on! What else?!
Huh?
No! Forget what I just said.
That came out wrong.
I just got tongue-tied!
Um...
Here. It's a day late, but take it.
O-Oh. Thanks.
You're still in love with Iori, right?
Yeah.
Did you feel obligated to go out with me after getting rejected?
No. That's just low.
Whether it's low or not is up for debate, in my opinion.
I don't know what I should do either.
My thoughts are a total train wreck.
But...
What I do know is that I love you.
Got it. You can look forward to White Day.
Don't worry, I am.
What the heck?!
Yui, you gave Taichi the same chocolate that you gave me?!
I-It was close!
It was close, so I couldn't give closure!
What do you mean by "closure"?
I can't let that slide.
Even though I seriously, absolutely, and without a doubt don't give a damn about Aoki.
You didn't need to emphasize it that heavily!
T-Taichi's done a lot for me this year.
I was just being nice!
There's no special meaning behind it!
Are you sure?
Yes!
I don't l-love him like that!
Though I absolutely love him as a friend!
"Absolutely," huh?
I told you, there's no special meaning behind it!
You must really love Taichi a lot, Inaba-chan.
Huh?
Got a problem with that?
No! No problem at all, Captain Inaba!
Anyway, Yui getting over her fear of men really was a good thing.
She was able to give obligatory chocolates to all the guys in her class yesterday.
Oh, yeah.
She even thought that some of the guys at the dojo were handsome and had nice stances.
Did you have to say that?!
What?! That's a huge problem for me!
Maybe I should start going to that dojo, too...
Okay, let's discuss what we'll be doing for our presentation.
How will we outdo the jazz band?
Let's start with some brainstorming.
I've got it!
The girls should cosplay as something sexy
to melt the brains of any male teachers and the guys on the student council—
I'll give your suggestion some thought if you can draw my sympathy by stripping naked and dancing.
How about presenting the most popular
articles from past issues of the CRC News?
But we won't be able to
beat the jazz band like that.
Yeah. They're going to perform
in front of the judges.
That'll leave one hell of an impression.
Why don't we make something major
specifically for the presentations?
We'll appeal to those stupid teachers
with that "Effort is more important than
achievement" crap that they love so much.
Those teachers would be heartbroken if they found out how crooked our efforts are.
The gap between your outer appearance and the darkness in your heart is too deep.
No, I didn't mean it like that.
I know!
How about running a special about the best places around school?
It'll take time to do the research, and we can publish it as a CRC News Extra.
Yeah.
Making something that really feels student-made should leave a good impression on them.
And it'll be useful information for everyone.
I think it's a good idea.
All right! We'll split up and start researching tomorrow.
We'll find interesting places around here and compile them into articles by the presentation date.
Sound good to you, President?
Yeah.
What's wrong, Iori?
You're totally not your normal self today!
Do I have to be my normal self?
I knew it.
I can't stay here.
They already have their own ideas about who "Nagase Iori" is.
I-Iori-chan?
Don't mind me.
I'll go home first.
W-Wait, Iori-chan!
I-Iori-chan, why are you trying to do the whole "cool beauty" thing now?
Trying to make a statement about how
Inaba-chan's given up on being the cool one?
What just happened, Aoki?
Were Iori's emotions transmitted to you?
I thought that the best thing I could do was just be myself.
If I did, then Yui and everyone else could go back to being themselves.
But that didn't accomplish anything.
Hello, Aoki-san.
I don't think I've ever called you "Aoki-san" before.
What do you want from me?
Aoki-san, what do you think of this phenomenon?
It's absolutely awful.
I'm sure.
So, what do you think you can do about it?
I can just be myself.
Isn't that the same as not doing anything?
N-No, there's meaning in it.
Ah. That wasn't quite right.
It's not that you're not doing anything,
it's that you can't do anything.
You're the most useless of the five.
Let me ask you again.
What do you think you can do?
You can't do anything, Aoki-san.
What are you going to do?
I wonder what Aoki's doing right now...
Yui!
If Yui's thinking about me, I can fight.
I can fight harder than anyone ever has!
I'll just be myself.
For me, for Yui, and for everyone,
I will do everything I can
for the club presentations.
You really are the most useless of the five.
You're not interesting.
Then just leave us all alone already!
Well...
That's all I had to say.
Maybe this will be the last
time I talk to you, Aoki-san.
Maybe.
Don't you dare patronize us!
The CRC won't move an inch from something like this.
Who asks me out and who I turn down is none of your business.
But would you really be okay with that, Inaba?
You're not the Iori we knew!
Bitch.
Maybe we should just disband the Cultural Research Club.
You probably think I'm a liar.